A Guide to the Papers of the Virginia Quarterly Review, 1925-1935
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
The Papers of the Virginia Quarterly Review 1925-1935
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-24/3/1.391
This collection consists of 1126 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection is a gift of the editor on January 12, 1939.
Scope and Content Information
The collection consists of correspondence with contributors during the editorship of James Southall Wilson (1925-1931) and part of the tenure of Stringfellow Barr (1931-1937). Included are almost all of the literary figures of this period, and many from other fields. Authors' original manuscripts together with proofs of almost every article and book review published in the Virginia Quarterly Review during this period. Proofs and manuscripts are filed in a separate sequence, chronologically by date of publication. A slip list of proofs and manuscripts is available in Special Collections.
Arrangement
Correspondence is filed alphabetically. Proofs and manuscripts are individually foldered and filed in a separate sequence, chronologically by date of publication.
Additional Descriptive Data
Additional Descriptive Data
Other Finding Aid
A slip list of proofs and manuscripts is available in the Special Collections Department.
Contents List
- Abbot, Willis J. 1927-1931, 23 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Abbott, Anne 1932, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Abbott, Charles David 1930-1935, 65 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Abernethy, Thomas Perkins 1931-1934, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Ackerson, Garret G., Jr. 1925-1930, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Adamic, Louis 1928-1935, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Adams, J. Donald 1932-1935, 23 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Adams, James Truslow 1929-1934, 43 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Adams, Martha Rivers 1926-1930, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Adams, William F. 1934-1935, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Addington, Luther 1931-1933, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Adler, Mortimer 1932, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Agar, Herbert 1935 December 20, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Agar (Box 1)
- Aiken, Conrad 1931-1934, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Aiken, J. Newton 1929-1931, 19 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Aird, Grace 1929-1931, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Albro, Mary 1930, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Alden, Ada 1930-1935, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Alden, Henry Mills 1927-1928, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Alderman, Edwin Anderson 1925-1931, 22 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Alderman, Mrs. Edwin 1931 May 5, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Alderman (Box 1)
- Aldington, Richard 1934, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Aldis, Graham 1927-1935, 56 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Alexander, Holmes M. 1933-1935, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Alexander, Miriam Campbell 1932-1933, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Allen, Grace B. 1934-1935, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Allen, George Leonard 1933-1934, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Allen, Hervey 1926-1934, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Allen, Jane 1930-1931, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Alling, Kenneth Slade 1928-1932, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Allinson, Brent Don 1930-1935, 23 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Altrocchi, Julia C. 1930-1934, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- American Civil Liberties Union 1931 January 13, 1 l. TLS, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- American College Bureau 1927 March 7, 2 l. TL, to [ Virginia Quarterly Review] (Box 1)
- American Foundation 1931-1932, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- American Scholar 1934, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Ames, Richard Sheridan 1934-1935, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Anderson, Ellen 1929-1933, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Anderson, Florence 1930-1933, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Anderson, Persis Greely 1930-1931, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Anderson, Robert L. 1929-1932, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 1)
- Anderson, Sherwood 1928-1934, 38 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Andrews, Charles M[clean]1925, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Andrews, F. Emerson 1929-1934, 34 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Andrews, George Lawrence 1925-1935, 43 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Andrews, Matthew Page 1930, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Angell, James Rowland 1925-1926, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Anshutz, Grace 1930, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Anthony, Katharine 1929-1933, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Appel, Benjamin 1931-1932, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Appleman, Jane 1930-1935, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Appleton, D. & Co. 1927-1934, 18 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Arata, Oliver S. 1931-1932, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Archer, Faye Bishop 1930, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Ardagh, Alice M. 1929, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Armstrong, Anne W. 1927-1930, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Armstrong, Hamilton Fish 1934, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Aronson, Moses J. 1935, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Arvin, Newton 1932-1935, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Ashe, S.A. 1926-1933, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Ashton, Randolph 1934-1935, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Asmus, Edna I. 1935, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Athearn, Clarence R. 1931-1935, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Atherton, Gertrude 1927, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Auden, Wystan Hugh 1935 September 23, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Auden (Box 2)
- Austin, Caroline F. 1930-1931, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Austin, Mary 1933, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Authors' Service Bureau 1934, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Avrett, Robert 1932-1934, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Aydelotte, Frank 1927-1934, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Ayers, Harry M. 1931-1933, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Ayres, C.E. 1934, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 2)
- Miscellaneous A, This file contains correspondence between Virginia Quarterly Review and the following authors:
  A & J. Literary Agency;Abbot, Frank;Abbot, Mrs. H. L.;Abbot, Mary Squire;Abramowitz, Isidore;Abramson, Daniel;Ackerman, Isabel;Adair, William;Adams, Charles Magee;Adams, Carl B.;Adams Grace;Adams, Gridley;Adams, John;Adams, M. Ray;Adams, Ruth;Addison, Mrs. D.D.;Adeney, Marcus;Agar, Edith;Aiken, Ralph;Aken, Rose;Alberts, S.S.;Albright, R.W.;Alden, Carroll S. ;Alden, Raymond M.;Alderson, A.T.;Alexander, Bessie Rowe;Alexander, Martha;Alexander, R. E.;Alfs, Genevieve;Alfonso, Arthemise Goertz;Allan, D. Maurice;Allen, Busby;Allen, Caroline R.;Allen, Eleanor;Allen, Gertrude;Allen, J.M.D., Jr.;Allen, J.O.;Allen, M. Chapin;Allen, Ruth;Alper, Benedict S.;Ambler, Charles H.;Ament, William S.;American Authors and Artist Agency;American Book Company;American Building Association News;American Mercury;Ames, Van Meter;Anderson, B.S.;Anderson, D.R.;Anderson, Frank H.;Anderson, Harold M.;Anderson, Jean Keller;Anderson, Laurence;Anderson, Rebecca;Anderson, W.N.;Anderson, W.T.;Andrade, M.J.;André, J.;Andrews, Harietta W.;Andrews, Laurence E.;Andrews, O.B.;Andrews, W.L.;Angell, C. Roy;Angus, B.R.;Angus, Frances R.;Angus, Marion I.;Antcliffe, Herbert;Anthony, Irvin;Annola, George;Antin, Mollie;Archer, Rosalie P.;Arell, Ruth;Arensberg, Charles;Armfield, Eugene;Armitage, D.M.;Armitage, Harold B.;Arant, Douglas;Armstrong, A.J.;Armstrong, F.R.A.;Armstrong, Virginia Irving;Armfield, Frank, Jr.;Arnold, C.P.;Arnold, Chloe;Arnold, George;Arnold Kathleen;Arnold, Malcolm H.;Arouet, J.S.;Arrowood, Charles Flinn;Arthos, John;Arthur, Marguerite;Ashburn, Andrew;Ashburn, Karl Everett;Ashburn, T.Q., Jr.;Ashe, Marjorie D.;Asheville Times;Ashley, Anne;Ashman, Margaret;Ashworth, Donna;Aslin, Colleen;Astley, Elizabeth;Aswell, Elizabeth;Athearn, Robert A.;Atkinson, J.H.;Auburn, Walter J.;Austin, Ethel;Author and Journalist;Avery, C.W.;Axford, Mary;Aydelotte, Dora;Aylett, L.D.;Ayre, Robert;Ayres, Charles G.;Ayres, Charles L.
- Babbitt, Irving 1929 October 8, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Babbitt (Box 3)
- Babcock, Charlotte F. 1925-1926, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Babcock, Havilah 1930-1932, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Bacon, Leonard 1927, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Baker, Harry T. 1926-1932, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Baker Newton D. 1924-1932, 20 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Baker, Ray Stannard 1925, 2 items. Letters, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Balch, Emily Clark 1927-1935, 132 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Baldwin, Howard 1931, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Ball, Thomas Fauntleroy 1930-1934, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Ball, W.W. 1933-1935, 17 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Balz, Albert G. A. 1933 September 14, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Balz (Box 3)
- Bardin, James Cook 1925-1933, 17 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Barkley, Murrell 1926 December 6, 1 l. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Barnes, Leonard 1931-1935, 20 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Barr, Stringfellow 1927-1935, 157 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review, chiefly with Lambert Davis (Box 3)
- Barringer, Paul Brandon 1931 May 19, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Barringer (Box 3)
- Barron, James S. 1929 September 4, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Barron (Box 3)
- Basso, Hamilton 1935, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Bates, H.E. 1930-1934, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Bates, Katherine Lee 1925-1929, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Bates, Sylvia Chatfield 1929-1933, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Battle, George Gordon 1925-1931, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Beach, Joseph Warren 1925-1934, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Beard, Charles Austin 1927-1935, 54 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Beard, William E. 1931-1933, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Beatty, Albert R. 1932, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Beatty, Richmond C. 1933-1935, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 3)
- Beacher, Marion E. 1930-1934, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Beer, Ethel S. 1935, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Beer, Thomas 1929 June 18, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Beer (Box 4)
- Beers, Henry Augustin 1925 January 20, 4 pp. ALS to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Beirne, Francis F. 1925-1931, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Belitt, Ben 1931-1934, 17 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Bell, Landon C. 1926-1931, 19 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Bell, Laurence 1935, 22 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Bellamann, Henry 1928-1934, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Benedict, Ruth 1935, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Benet, Laura 1933 October 23, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Benet (Box 4)
- Bennett, Gertrude Ryder 1927-1929, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Bennett, John 1930-1934, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Bent, Silas 1930-1935, 33 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Berenberg, David P. 1927, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Betts, Thomas Jeffries 1930-1934, 70 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Bevan, Ralph H. 1930-1931, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Bidwell, W.E. 1931-1932, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Bigelow, Paultney 1927-1931, 44 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Binkley, Robert C. 1931-1935, 53 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Bishop, John Peale 1932-1935, 44 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Björkman, Edwin 1926-1933, 40 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Blackford, Launcelot Minor 1931-1933, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Blackmur, Richard P. 1935, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Blackwell, R.E. 1925-1927, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Blankner, Frederickea 1925-1935, 45 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Blayney, Lindsey 1925-1926, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Bluen, Herbert 1930-1931, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Bobbs-Merrill Co. 1926-1934, 37 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Boissevain, Eugen 1927 July 14, 1 l. TLS, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Bolling, Irene Johnson 1932, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 4)
- Bond, Richmond P. 1933-1935, 34 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 5)
- Bondurant, Alexander L. 1925-1935, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 5)
- Boni & Liveright 1927-1931, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 5)
- Booker, Betty 1926 July 23, 1 l. TLS, Helen Stockdell to Booker, w/envelope to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 5)
- Booker, Betty 1926 November 10, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Booker (Box 5)
- Borah, William Edgar 1929, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 5)
- Bottome, Phyllis 1927, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 5)
- Bourne, Henry E. 1930-1931, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 5)
- Bowers, Claude G. 1926-1931, 26 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 5)
- Bowie, W. Russell 1925-1927, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 5)
- Bowman, Louise Morey 1929-1934, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 5)
- Boyd, Ernest 1927-1932, 32 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 5)
- Boyd, Eva Phillips 1928-1933, 16 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 5)
- Boyd, Thomas 1927 January 12, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Boyd (Box 5)
- Boynton, Percy Holmes 1925-1930, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 5)
- Bradford, Gamalial 1924-1931, 33 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 5)
- Bradford, Roark, and Mrs. Bradford 1930-1935, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 5)
- Braithwaite, William Stanley 1926, 6 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 5)
- Brameld, Theodore 1935, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 5)
- Brande, Dorothea 1931-1932, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 5)
- Brandt & Brandt 1924-1930, 175 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 5)
- Brandt & Brandt 1931-1935, 266 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 5)
- Brashear, M.M. 1935, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 6)
- Brewer, Warren, and Putnam 1930-1932, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 6)
- Brewton, William W. 1928, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 6)
- Brickell, Herschel 1928-1935, 26 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 6)
- Bridges, J. Malcolm 1929-1930, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 6)
- Brooke, Tucker 1925, 3 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 6)
- Brooks, Cleanth 1934-1935, 17 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 6)
- Brooks, Van Wyck 1924-1934, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 6)
- Brooks, Eleanor V. (Mrs. Van Wyck) 1930-, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 6)
- Brown, Armstead 1929, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 6)
- Curtis Brown, Ltd. 1925-1930, 149 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 6)
- Curtis Brown, Ltd. 1931-1935, 148 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 6)
- Brown, Ford K. 1933-1934, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 6)
- Brown, Kenneth 1929-1933, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 6)
- Brown, Sydney M. 1931-1934, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 6)
- Brownlow, Louis 1931, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 6)
- Bruce, Kathleen 1929-1934, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 6)
- Bruce, Philip Alexander 1925-1930, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 6)
- Bruce, William Cabell 1924-1933, 65 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 6)
- Brucker, Herbert 1930, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 7)
- Bryan, John 1926-1934, 57 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review, w/enclosed poems (Box 7)
- Bryan, John Stewart 1929, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 7)
- Buchanan, Scott 1930-1934, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 7)
- Buck, Philo, Jr. 1925-1927, 16 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 7)
- Buell, Raymond Leslie 1931-1935, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 7)
- Burgum, Edwin Berry 1927-1930, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 7)
- Burke, Kenneth 1932-1935, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 7)
- Burklund, C.E. 1931, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 7)
- Burrell, Angus 1929, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 7)
- Burt, Struthers 1925-1931, 2 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 7)
- Butler, James M. 1929-1930, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 7)
- Butler, Nicholas Murray 1929-1934, 3 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 7)
- Buxbaum, Katherine 1931, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 7)
- Bynner, Witter 1925-1935, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 7)
- Byrd, Harry Flood 1926-1934, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 7)
- Miscellaneous Ba-Bh 1925-1935, ca. 700 items. Miscellaneous authors, correspondence, chiefly rejection letters, with Virginia Quarterly Review. (Box 7)
- Miscellaneous Bi-By (Box 8)
- Cabell, James Branch 1925-1934, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Caldwell, Erskine 1934 December 29, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Caldwell (Box 9)
- Calverton, Victor Francis 1926-1930, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Cambiaire, C.P. 1928, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Campbell, A.S. 1929-1931, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Campbell, Killis 1927-1929, 2 items. TL(carbons), Virginia Quarterly Review to Campbell (Box 9)
- Campbell, Roy 1934 December 7, 1 l. TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Campbell (Box 9)
- Canby, Mr. & Mrs. Henry Seidel 1925-1935, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Cane, Melville H. 1925-1934, 28 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Cantwell, Robert 1935, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Cape, Jonathan, and Harrison Smith 1929-1931, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Capper, Arthur 1931 November 21, 1 l. TLS, to Virginia Quarterly Review. (Box 9)
- Carner, Robert J. 1929, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Carrington, Mary Coles 1925-1935, 32 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Carson, Mrs. James 1930, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Carver, Gertrude Nason 1926-1932, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Casamajor, Louis 1934, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Cason, Clarence E. 1928-1934, 89 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Cates, Dudley 1933, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Cather, Willa 1925 February 13, 1 l. TLS, to Virginia Quarterly Review. (Box 9)
- Causton, Bernard 1931-1932, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Century Company 1926-1932, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Chafee, Zechariah 1931-1933, 20 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Chalmers, Gordon K 1934-1935, 16 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Chamberlain, John 1935, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Chamberlayne, C.G. 1933, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Chamberlin, Ernest V. 1926-1929, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)
- Chambers, Lenoir 1925-1930, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 9)